# Michelle Meighen

# Snippet about me

I like helping people solve their problems with a positive attitude. The challenge of doing research and applying it to the problem at hand is something I enjoy. I'm a quick and eager learner that is highly coachable. I'm a happy go lucky person and have built lastings relationships with many of my past coworkers. Ready to be part of a team and grow with a company.



(260) 450-9766



1054 Lismore S. Dr Apt B Indianapolis, IN 46227

michmeig11@gmail.com

in Linkedin.com/in/michelle-meighen-82573b5b

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Northern Hoosier Marketing-Sales and Marketing Directv and At&t Internet

Feb 2020 - currently

We handle the sales of Directv and AT&T internet in Costco stores. We work individually and as a team to achieve set goals for the week or month. We interact with a wide variety of people and I've quickly learned how to build rapport with a potential customer. I enjoy talking about what we have to offer and working with them to close the sale.

- Client acquisition and retention
- Communication
- Product Knowledge
- Problem Solving

## Veterans Lawn & Landscaping LLC, Fort Wayne-Landscape Crew Leader/ General Labor

May 2019 - Feb 2020

Meet with potential clients one on one, discuss what they would like to have done, and write up the estimate for the job. Once the client has agreed with the price, I am responsible for the materials needed, overseeing the job process, working with my coworkers, and completing the job with quality work. Also, I am utilized as a float crew member and able to help out where I'm needed.

- Creative
- Time Management
- Flexibility
- Problem Solving

### **Keystone Rv / Dutchmen RV, Goshen, IN** — Shelling department

October 2017 - May 2019

You learn different levels of discipline and determination when you hold a fast paced factory job. It also gave me a high level of appreciation for my past jobs and any future ones I will have. This job may not have provided me with technical skills, but the personal growth I obtained will shape my future from here on out.

• Commitment to personal goals

## K&K Insurance, Fort Wayne, IN - Operation Specialists I

January 2016 - October 2017

My hard work as a temp contractor at K&K lead to them offering me a permanent job. This new position includes the same duties that I held before with the addition of handling the onboarding process for new hires. This consists of filling out the initial form for equipment and phone requirements, following up on tickets, and making sure the new hire has what they need to do their job. Taking on this duty has helped me improve my organization and communication skills because, when issues arise, I became a middle man between the hiring manager and the tech company.

- Troubleshooting
- Communication
- Time Management
- Organized

# Aon/ K&K Insurance, Fort Wayne, IN - Policy Processor

February 2015 - January 2016

Since starting at AON as a Policy Processor I have honed my skills in Microsoft Office programs and have also become efficient in both of their operating databases; As400 and AuMine. For both of these, I am responsible for multiple daily reports and, when needed, collecting required paperwork from agencies. I also help troubleshoot small issues that need researched or fixed in both systems.

- Helper
- Research
- Quick Learner
- Detailed Data Entry

## Veterans Lawn & Landscaping LLC, Fort Wayne-Landscape Crew Leader

May 2013 - February 2015

I have worked my way up at Veteran's from general labor to Landscape Crew Leader. I now meet with potential clients one on one, discuss what they would like to have done, and write up the estimate for the job. Once the client has agreed with the price, I am responsible for the materials needed for each job, overseeing and working with my coworkers, and completing the job with quality work.

- Creative
- Time Management
- Flexibility
- Problem Solving

### Head JV Softball Coach, Leo, IN -Head Jv Softball Coach

March 2014 - June 2014

Coached young and very talented girls for the season. I helped them hone their skills and pushed them to excel in their school work as well. The best parts of the jobs were watching the growth of the girls in softball and as individuals.

- Being a motivator
- Decision maker
- Support

# **Evans Equipment, Butler, IN** -Customer Service Rep

March 2012 - May 2013

As a CSR at Evans I handled freight for multiple accounts. It was a fast paced environment with updating customers and brokers regarding their freight status, booking freight, brokering freight, and entering freight information once received. I built relationships with carriers and brokers to give our customers the best customer service I could provide.

- Experienced in Office ProgramsMultitaskingPositive Attitude

- Adaptable

#### VOLUNTEERING

Bethany Christian Schools Goshen, In - High School Assistant Softball Coach in 2018 and was offered a paying position for 2019 season.

#### **EDUCATION**

Indiana Purdue University Of Fort Wayne, Fort Wayne - Coursework in Art Education

August 2005 - February 2012

Northrop High School, Fort Wayne - High School Graduate

Graduated in May 2005 diploma

### REFERRALS AND REFERENCES

Kenny Girardot - Friend and boss at Veteran's Lawn and Landscaping

— Kenny and I have known each other for 10+ years. He has been a great friend and boss over the years.

Cell - 260-312-4236

Melissa Kimmel - Distribution Clerk at Nipsco

- I have known Melissa going on 6 years now. We started playing softball together and have grown into friends over the years.

Cell - 260-242-0999

James Bailey - IT Support Specialist

- Jim and I worked together at K&K Insurance. Even though we were in different departments we would communicate daily on users' issues and the incoming hires' setup process.

Cell - 260-416-4504

Cynthia Sabo - Office Service Assistant/ Compliance

- Cindy trained me on the operating systems when I first started at K&K as a temp and helped me through any questions I had.

Work - 260-459-5766